<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Applicants><Applicant><Name>Mini Aggarwal</Name><Email>agr.mini@gmail.com</Email><Phone>646-942-0535</Phone><Location>10810 167th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052</Location><Country>USA</Country><PositionCategory>Design: Physical Design</PositionCategory><University>['Illinois Institute of Technology (IIT), Chicago, IL', 'Bangalore Institute of Technology, India']</University><Degree>['M.S, Electrical Engineering', 'Bachelor of Engineering, Electronics and Communications']</Degree><GraduationYear>['2007', '2004']</GraduationYear><YearsExperience>12</YearsExperience><JobIntention>full-time</JobIntention><VisaStatus>--</VisaStatus><Able>no</Able><Subject>Resume for Physical design roles</Subject><DateSent>04-22-2025</DateSent><NotableCompanies>Intel</NotableCompanies><TopSkills>Technical Expertise - Physical Design, Floorplanning, STA, Timing Closure, Low-Power Design, Program Management – Project Planning, Risk Mitigation, Agile/Waterfall Execution, Silicon Development Lifecycle – RTL to GDSII, Tape-Out, DFT, Stakeholder Communication – Executive Reporting, Milestone Tracking, Resource Planning, Cross-Functional Leadership – Coordination across design, verification, layout teams, Vendor &amp; Partner Engagement – Foundry (TSMC, Intel), EDA (Synopsys, Cadence), IP Integration</TopSkills><GPTSummary>Accomplished silicon design professional with over 12 years of experience managing SoC IPs for Intel™ Server product line. Successfully delivered multiple ASIC tape-outs by driving execution across cross-functional teams, managing risk, and ensuring milestone alignment. Adept at program planning, stakeholder coordination, and technical execution oversight in complex ASIC development programs.</GPTSummary><FolderPath>Applicants/USA/Design/Physical Design/Mini Aggarwal: 04-22-2025</FolderPath><Resume>Yes</Resume><DesiredJobRole>Physical Design Lead</DesiredJobRole></Applicant><Applicant><Name>Balaji Navalpakkam Kannan</Name><Email>nkbalaji01@gmail.com</Email><Phone>864-328-5837</Phone><Location>Austin, TX</Location><Country>USA</Country><PositionCategory>Other</PositionCategory><University>['The University of Chicago Booth School of Business', 'Clemson University', 'Anna University']</University><Degree>['Master of Business Administration', 'Master of Science, Electrical Engineering', 'Bachelor of Engineering, Electrical and Electronic Engineering']</Degree><GraduationYear>['2025', '2009', '2006']</GraduationYear><YearsExperience>15</YearsExperience><JobIntention>full-time</JobIntention><VisaStatus>--</VisaStatus><Able>no</Able><Subject>Business Development &amp; Strategic Partnerships Lead</Subject><DateSent>04-22-2025</DateSent><NotableCompanies>Intel Corporation, NXP Semiconductor, Infosys</NotableCompanies><TopSkills>Strategic Partnership Development, IP Licensing &amp; SoC Integration, Technical &amp; Commercial Negotiations, Semiconductor Ecosystem Expertise, Cross-Functional Leadership, Go-to-Market Strategy &amp; Customer Engagement</TopSkills><GPTSummary>Balaji is a dynamic business development leader with experience in silicon product innovation and strategic partnerships across the semiconductor ecosystem. He has proven expertise in SoC design, IP licensing, OEM/EDA collaboration, and go-to-market strategy. He is adept at negotiating technical and commercial agreements, leading cross-functional teams, and communicating effectively with both engineering and executive stakeholders.</GPTSummary><FolderPath>Applicants/USA/Other/Balaji Navalpakkam Kannan: 04-22-2025</FolderPath><Resume>Yes</Resume><DesiredJobRole>Business Development and Strategic Partnerships Lead</DesiredJobRole></Applicant><Applicant><Name>Bhargava Saketh Nagapattinam</Name><Email>bhargava.saketh@gmail.com</Email><Phone>945-257-1050</Phone><Location>Novi, MI 48374</Location><Country>USA</Country><PositionCategory>Architecture</PositionCategory><University>['The University of Texas at Dallas', 'Osmania University']</University><Degree>['Master of Science in Computer Engineering', 'Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics and Communication &amp; Engineering']</Degree><GraduationYear>['2024', '2022']</GraduationYear><YearsExperience>2</YearsExperience><JobIntention>full-time</JobIntention><VisaStatus>--</VisaStatus><Able>no</Able><Subject>Intersted of joining AheadComputing!</Subject><DateSent>04-22-2025</DateSent><NotableCompanies>Defense Research and Development Laboratory, Silicon Engineers, Bright Mind Enrichment</NotableCompanies><TopSkills>Verilog, SystemVerilog, C, C++, Python Scripting, TCL, Perl, MySQL, UVM, Object Oriented Programming (OOPs), SPI, I2C, UART, AMBA (AXI, AHB, APB), USB, PCIe</TopSkills><GPTSummary>Bhargava Saketh Nagapattinam is a highly skilled Computer Engineer with a Master's degree from The University of Texas at Dallas and a Bachelor's degree from Osmania University. He has experience working with notable companies like Defense Research and Development Laboratory and Silicon Engineers. His top skills include Verilog, SystemVerilog, C, C++, Python Scripting, and more. He is seeking a full-time position as a CPU Performance Architect.</GPTSummary><FolderPath>Applicants/USA/Architecture/Bhargava Saketh Nagapattinam: 04-22-2025</FolderPath><Resume>Yes</Resume><DesiredJobRole>CPU Performance Architect</DesiredJobRole></Applicant><Applicant><Name>Chrysanthos Pepi</Name><Email>cpepis@tamu.edu</Email><Phone>+1 979-985-1329</Phone><Location>College Station, TX, 77840</Location><Country>USA</Country><PositionCategory>Other</PositionCategory><University>['Texas A&amp;M University', 'University of Cyprus']</University><Degree>['Doctor of Philosophy in Computer Engineering', 'Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering']</Degree><GraduationYear>2025</GraduationYear><YearsExperience>6</YearsExperience><JobIntention>full-time</JobIntention><VisaStatus>--</VisaStatus><Able>no</Able><Subject>Interested of joining AheadComputing!</Subject><DateSent>04-22-2025</DateSent><NotableCompanies>Texas A&amp;M University, Intel Corporation, AMD, Intel Labs, KIOS Centre of Excellence – University of Cyprus, multicore Computer Architecture Laboratory – University of Cyprus</NotableCompanies><TopSkills>C, C++, Python, Bash, Git</TopSkills><GPTSummary>Chrysanthos Pepi is a Doctor of Philosophy in Computer Engineering student at Texas A&amp;amp;M University, expected to graduate in 2025. He has worked at notable companies such as Texas A&amp;amp;M University, Intel Corporation, AMD, and Intel Labs. His top skills include programming languages such as C, C++, Python, and Bash, as well as version control with Git.</GPTSummary><FolderPath>Applicants/USA/Other/Chrysanthos Pepi: 04-22-2025</FolderPath><Resume>Yes</Resume><DesiredJobRole>Computer Engineering Researcher</DesiredJobRole></Applicant><Applicant><Name>Rutujeet Bhagvant Falmare</Name><Email>rutujeetfalmare28@gmail.com</Email><Phone>--</Phone><Location>--</Location><Country>--</Country><PositionCategory>Other</PositionCategory><University>--</University><Degree>Master's Computer Science</Degree><GraduationYear>--</GraduationYear><YearsExperience>--</YearsExperience><JobIntention>full-time</JobIntention><VisaStatus>--</VisaStatus><Able>no</Able><Subject>Inquiry About New Grad SDE Opportunities at Ahead Computing</Subject><DateSent>04-22-2025</DateSent><NotableCompanies /><TopSkills>Software Development, API's, Hardware Systems, Web Technologies</TopSkills><GPTSummary>Rutujeet Bhagvant Falmare is a recent Master's Computer Science graduate with a strong interest in software development. He has experience working on projects involving APIs, hardware systems, and web technologies. He is eager to contribute to a fast-paced startup environment and grow alongside a passionate team.</GPTSummary><FolderPath>Applicants/OtherOrUnknown/Other/Rutujeet Bhagvant Falmare: 04-22-2025</FolderPath><Resume>No</Resume><DesiredJobRole>Software Development Engineer</DesiredJobRole></Applicant></Applicants>